Welcome to Microsoft System Engineer and Cloud Administrator tutorial.
My name is Galvin Johnson and I will be your instructor for this tutorial.
Before I begin, let me give you a little review about my IT background.
In the year 2008, between the year 2008 and 2012,
I studied System and Network Management in the Netherlands.
It's actually a four-year full-time program.
So, I've done my study in the Netherlands and now moved to Belgium.
Between the year 2012 and 2013, I also studied an IT system engineer.
Of course, I thought it was a part-time training,
which I obtained a diploma from that school in the University in Cartwright.
Between the year 2014, 2017, I studied network management from highest to shown here in Antwerp in Belgium.
So, I was actually going to evening classes.
It's actually a three-year, three-year program.
So, during my study, when I moved, when I went to Belgium from the Netherlands,
so I started working as an IT service desk support engineer from 2012 to 2016.
So, after I went to upgrade myself, I went to school to highest to shown
and obtain some certificates and also a diploma in System and Network Engineering.
I decided to have, I probably went to work for a different company,
which I was from transitioning to 2019.
I worked as an IT system administrator.
Then, from 2019, to your data, I've been working as an IT system administrator
for a different company, as a consultant,
where I've been sent to different multinational companies.
So, with my IT background, I'll be giving you a more practical training on system engineering
and cloud administrator.
This is going to be a training tutorial in details of IT
and pure particles with little theory.